

# Benjamin Marzęcki A Student looking for a parttime job

Risdalsvej 40 st.21, 8260, Viby J

benjamin.marzecki@gmail.com  $\square$ 

+45 91 76 67 64

## **LANGUAGE**

Polish - Native

English - C1

German - A2

Danish - A2

## **COMPETENCIES**

Communication

Time Management

Availability

Commitment

Communication

**Teamwork** 

## **PROFILE**

I am a 19-year-old student from Poland, currently pursuing a degree in Multimedia Design at Business Academy Aarhus. I am highly organized, detail-oriented, and confident in my ability to swiftly adapt and overcome challenges. My goal is to gain valuable experience while contributing to the tasks I undertake.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Production worker** • Hunter Douglas Fabrication

Full Time

06.2023 - 08.2023

My main duties consisted of:

- · Assembly works in the production of internal window coverings such as roller blinds and verticals
- · manual work such as cutting, gluing, addition of components
- Packing, transport from production departments to the warehouse
- · scanning, completing orders, combining and securing packages during transport
- · marking goods with appropriate labels
- using a hydraulic press to reduce the volume of used elements.

## Confectionery Assistant • Cukiernia Sowa - Pastry Shop

Part Time

07.2022 - 09.2022

My responsibilities included:

 handling customer inquiries and concerns promptly and professionally, weighing, pricing and packaging items and maintaining cleanliness.

#### **EDUCATION**

Multimedia Design • Business Academy Aarhus AP Degree

09.2023 - ongoing

I'm currently engaged in a Multimedia Design program that's all about web design, coding, and creating digital interface. What sets this program apart is its hands-on focus, where we tackle projects together in teams, making collaboration a key part of the learning experience.